wadja.com 2012-03-29

# 

Effective: December 8, 2009

**About Wadja**

Wadja Media Limited develops services that make the message distribution process easier across multiple devices and platforms. Wadja Media is deeply committed to enhancing the social networking experience by providing mechanisms to deliver real time information across the web and remove the 'noise' associated with multiple streams of conversation (pages) by delivering focused social, keyword, semantic value to subscribers (label followers)

Wadja Media Limited owns and operates www.wadja.com, a unique messaging service based on shared topics of page and activities. Use Wadja.com to follow profile "labels" that focus around the hobbies and group discussions you enjoy most.)

Page conversations can take place over the Web, Email and SMS, and the responses are shared between contacts, or privately with a friend.

Wadja cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@wadja.com](mailto:privacy@wadja.com).

**Information Collection and Use by Wadja**

Wadja collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Wadja service. Wadja also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal pages, gender, age, mobile number and location in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other.

Wadja also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the Wadja social networking and media community. Email addresses and mobile numbers are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Wadja , to add users to members contact networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network.

Many of Wadja 's services work with SMS messaging. You can earn free points and use them to send text (sms) messages to a mobile number. Likewise Wadja provides a messaging service through SMS Gateways providers that allow registered Wadja users to send SMS by adding a + symbol, a mobile country code, and the number of the message recipient.

This service is strictly offered to Wadja members and as a Graphical User Interface between the web and Gateway Providers. Wadja provides this interface to all users who have verified their email and mobile number account and in no way assumes any responsibility for the actions of individual users and their messaging habits. Any reports of abuse will result in Wadja discontinuing user’s accounts without any notification whatsoever. Each user takes FULL RESPONSIBILITY for the destination and content of each and every message they send through the Wadja GUI web interface.

Wadja's SMS messaging service is strictly optional and Wadja is in no way liable or responsible for any misrepresentation or misuse of mobile phone numbers or wrong mobile numbers. Wadja will never use our SMS messaging service for SMS spamming or telemarketing. However, some SMS providers who offer free services in your region may be ad-supported. If you use these services you agree to their terms and conditions. Wadja may also include Message Ads within notifications and email alerts and private messaging between friends in and outside of the network. Any user sending SMS messages through the Wadja GUI interface understands that they are responsible, as senders, for any complaints or disputes that a recipient may have with the advertisements that accompany the message. Wadja users do not have to use the free service and understand that ad supported messaging provides them with free message sending rights.

Keep in mind that you can make your mobile number invisible to your contact list, but still receive messages, since your contacts only see your Wadja ID as a 'Send to' option in their SMS contact list. Your mobile number will only be available to your contacts in your network. Wadja assumes no responsibility, nor is legally liable for any damage, whether personal or professional, for any late delivery or failed delivery of SMS messages.

Should you decide to display mobile phone number to your contact list, Wadja is in no way legally liable or responsible for any misuse or abuse of your displayed mobile phone number. You always have the choice to make your mobile number visible or invisible by choosing Everyone, Friends or No One in the 'Make your mobile visible to…' box, found in your ACCOUNT, My account, Notify and Verify section of the service. If you choose ‘No One’ from the list people can send you SMS but they cannot see your number from your Profile page. Of course you can remove your number altogether, which would still let you send SMS to your contact list but not receive SMS from then in return. You can always select the types of SMS alerts you want to receive by going to ACCOUNT (My Account, Notify and Verify) section after you sign in, and choosing the check box alert notifications accordingly.

Users within a personal network communicate on Wadja with each other through Wadja.com , without disclosing their personal email addresses. Upon registration each member is allocated a personal Wadja domain URL (http://wadja.com/'yourname') and a personal Wadja email address ('yourname'@wadja.com) Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members unless full names are added in their personal details section. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Wadja allows users to search for other members using their Wadja ID, first and last name, and email address.

Upon sign up, a users first two pages are already shown (your location and profile photo). A variety of other System Pages are provided to help users archive and organize their social content and streams of real-time communication.

System pages are set by Wadja and determine what pages the user will automatically receive. Wadja ’s system pages are Notes, Message, Location and a few more.

Be aware that "Notes" and some other System Pages on Wadja are available for everyone to see. Whether you send a Note @someone or just update your Notes on a label or your profile, the notes are publicly available and will be displayed for everyone to see. Do not post notes that are private or sensitive to yourself or another user. If you wish to write something private to another users or contacts, use the @ symbol to send a private message.

You can change who views your pages and the "Everyone" settings by going to the SETTING (Pages) page. Here you can choose whom you would like to make the labels available to: No one, only me, custom, or everyone.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their notification setting to not receive notification emails or SMS messages in the user SETTINGS (Notify and Verify) section.

From time to time, Wadja or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on the Wadja web properties. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

**Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members**

Wadja members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. Wadja stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the contacts list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. Wadja does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders (up to three(3) per email address). Recipients of invitations from Wadja may contact Wadja to request the removal of their information from our database.

Wadja members may also store email addresses and mobile number of people they know in their internal Wadja address book and may also choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses.

User also have an option of storing and backing up contact usernames and passwords from other sites and services, and mobile devices from which they wish to aggregate friends and contacts into their Wadja contact list for messaging and storage purposes. Users who elect to aggregate contact lists from 3rd party services and devices are fully responsible for this maintained list.

You may prevent Wadja email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by sending a single email with the subject 'BLOCK' to privacy@wadja.com. Please note that the email must come from the account you wish to block.

**Use of Cookies**

Wadja uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the 'Help' menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from Wadja in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that Wadja allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Wadja Privacy Policy.

**Links**

Wadja contains links to sites. Wadja is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Wadja.

**Chat Rooms, Journals and WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds and Public Forums**

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**

Wadja users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account settings.

**Email Choice/Opt-out**

Members who no longer wish to receive updates or notifications may choose not to by selecting to not receive notification emails or SMS alerts in the ACCOUNT (My Account, Notify and Verify) sections. Users who do not wish to receive Wadja newsletters or blog updates may choose not to by selecting to not receive Wadja information by clicking on the 'remove' link from the relevant email. All notification emails, SMS messages and Wadja newsletters and blog updates also include the above instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future.

**Third Party Advertising**

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by Wadja or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Wadja and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Security**

Wadja member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. Wadja takes precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on Wadja , please contact us at [privacy@wadja.com](mailto:privacy@wadja.com).

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information Wadja.com Collects**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Wadja will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Wadja , whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Wadja Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Wadja reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in page that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Wadja or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the 'Changes in Our Privacy Policy' section below.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: [privacy@wadja.com](mailto:privacy@wadja.com).
